- Good! You guys are all here.
- Hey, what's up?
Well, I have a job interview
at Ralph Lauren tomorrow.
- Oh!
- Congratulations!
Oh, boy.
That guy's underwear sucks!
- What?
- Well, I got this pair marked "XS."
Let me tell you, there was no room
for excess anything in there.
Anyway, I'm gonna be the coordinator
of the women's collection.
I'll work right under the director.
It's the perfect job for me.
Wow. Well, if you nail the interview,
you'll get it.
- Yeah.
- Want to work on your interview skills?
- Okay!
- Okay! Let's start with the handshake.
- Hi.
Very good handshake.
Good wrist action.
- Thank you.
- Let me try.
Okay.
Oh, my God!
What did I ever do to you?
Did I squeeze too hard?
Let's just say
I'm glad I'm not Chandler.
That's right, Ross. I can see you
in your new apartment. You see me.
Same as yesterday,
same as the day before.
Is he doing his "shark attack" bit yet?
No. Oh, wait! There he goes.
Very funny, Ross.
Very lifelike and funny. Okay.
Oh, no, no, no.
I wasn't waving at you, lady.
Whoa, maybe I was. Hey!
Monica, this hot girl in Ross' building
is flirting with me.
Get in there, man.
Flirt back. Mix it up!
Yeah, I'm down with that.
Okay, here it goes.
How...
...you...
...doing?
It worked! She's waving me over.
I'll be right over.
Let's see,
she's on the third floor...
Wow.
- She is pretty, huh?
- Tell me about it, huh?
Oh, no, no.
No, no! I'm not with her.
Oh, that's just Monica.
Blah!
Hey, Joey!
Great stuff, huh?
- This is your place?
- Yeah, of course it is. Oh, come on in.
Ooh, ohh. Uh, go by the window.
You can pretend to be surfing.
But I counted.
You're not supposed to live here.
Oh, man!
- Unh!
- What happened?
I ended up at Ross' place.
I must have miscounted or something.
Damn! She's not there anymore.
Oh, look, Ross is doing
his "watching TV" bit.
No, Joe, I think he's just watching TV.
We've lost visual contact with the suspect.
Okay, now I really have to go.
It's so unfair that
our date has to get cut short...
...just because some guy
shot at a store clerk.
- I know, but it's my job.
- Then maybe I could come too?
Suspect has
just emerged naked from the sewer.
All right, you go.
- Bye-bye.
- Okay. Bye.
- Oh, God!
- What?
Oh, I just miss him so much!
Wow.
For just a week,
you guys are close, huh?
Yeah, it's weird.
I can't help it, though. He's so sweet.
He's like this little puppy dog, you know?
But like a really tough one
who shoots bad guys.
Ugh, I love the beginning parts
of relationships, you know?
You can't keep your hands
off each other.
- I know. It is the best. Ha, ha.
- Ha, ha.
God, how long did that last
for you and Chandler?
What? It's still going on.
Come on, seriously.
When did it end?
I am serious. We're all over
each other all the time.
Okay, you know where you are
better than I do. I was just curious.
Why don't you just calm down,
Phoebe, all right?
Get all your facts before you tell
everybody you're the only hot couple.
God, I woke the beast. Um...
I was wrong obviously.
I just misspoke. It's okay.
Well, it is okay. I mean...
As long as you know Chandler and I
are also hot and fiery.
I mean, just as hot as you.
I mean, our flame...
Whoo! It is on fire!
Monica, here's your broom back.
You are so cute.
- Oh, hey! How'd the interview go?
- Ugh!
Horrible! I did the stupidest,
most embarrassing thing.
Did you tell the guy you wanted to have sex
with his wife then fall off your chair?
- No.
- So, what happened?
Ugh, it was horrible!
And the interview part went so well.
You know, like, I even made him laugh.
He said something about a boat...
...and I was like, "Well, yeah,
if you've got enough life jackets."
Trust me. It was actually very funny.
Anyway, so we were
saying goodbye and, uh... Ugh.
- What happened?
- All right, we were shaking hands...
...and he kind of leaned in toward me.
Maybe he was going to open the door.
But I totally misread him and I, uh...
You kissed him?
I didn't know what else to do!
Well, you could have tried...
...not kissing him.
Thanks, Chandler.
Hey, Rach,
a guy from Ralph Lauren called.
You got a second interview.
- I can't believe it! I got a second interview.
- Yes!
That kiss isn't looking like
such a mistake now, is it?
Wait a minute, wait. You don't think
that's why he wants me back?
Yeah!
No?
Kiss? What are you talking about?
Ugh, I accidentally kissed him
in the interview...
...and now he wants me back of course...
...because, "Let's bring back
the girl who kisses everybody"!
Come on, Rach.
What if he thinks I'm the kind of girl
that'll just sleep with him?
He wants you back
because you're right for the job.
Maybe. I don't know. Oh, God!
How could I be so stupid?
Oh, Rachel, look, don't say that.
I think you just need a hug
from Joey. Heh.
Come on. Come on, ha-ha-ha.
She's back! Hot girl's back!
Aw, well, I'm not totally back yet.
But I appreciate it.
No, in Ross' building. She's back!
She's back!
Okay, wait there. I'll be over in a second.
One, two, three. Got it!
I gotta check out this hot girl.
There she is!
Damn it! Did you move?
Yes.
I lived with you for a while.
Then I found this place.
I'm Ross.
Yes?
Uh...
Do you happen to have
a hot girl in there?
No, I'm all alone.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Oh. Hey, little girl.
Is your mommy or sister or babysitter
by any chance, a hot girl?
- Daddy!
- Later, girl! Aah.
Oh, man!
Hot girl?
Hot girl!
- Hi, Rachel. Come on in.
- Hi. Okay.
- Ahem.
- It's nice to see you again.
Thank you.
Oh, Rachel, uh...
- What?
- Just, uh...
- Excuse me?
- Yeah, let me...
Whoa, eh, oh!
All right. Okay, I see what's going on here.
Now, listen, look...
...I am sorry if I gave you
the wrong impression.
But I am not some hussy who will
just sleep around to get ahead.
- Now... Eh, eh!
- Well...
Even though I kissed you,
that does not give you...
...the right to demand sex from me!
I do not want this job that bad.
Good day, sir.
Ugh, you are not gonna believe...
...what that sleazeball
from Ralph Lauren did to me.
Okay, that's amazing.
How did you know that?
You got ink on your lip.
Oh.
What do you say, maybe,
sometime I hold your gun?
I don't know.
We're not supposed to do that.
What could happen? I mean...
Yeah. I'm gonna say no.
Do you want to see a movie
after dinner tonight?
Oh, we can't. We already have plans.
What are you doing?
Um, well, same thing we did all day.
Just hang out at Gary's apartment.
He is so amazing.
We never left the bedroom.
But have fun at the movie.
Uh, ha, ha.
Well, we're not seeing a movie.
You're not? Why did you ask us
if we wanted to go?
Oh, um, because I just wanted
to know what you were doing...
...so you wouldn't walk in
on me and Chandler...
...while we were doing it all night.
- Will you excuse me just a second? Okay.
- Yeah.
Chandler? Can I see you for a second?
- Uh, yeah.
- Okay, heh.
- We have got to beat them!
- Why?
Because Gary and Phoebe think
they're a hotter couple than we are.
- Oh! So?
- So?
So we've gotta go have a lot of sex
and prove them wrong!
You have got to stop this
competitive thing. It's crazy.
Just to impress Gary and Phoebe...
...you want me to go upstairs
and have sex over and over...
...and I'm saying no to this why?
Get your coat!
- Hey.
- Hi.
Excuse me.
You should check this out.
Tell the other tenants.
Apparently, he's running around
looking for some kind of hot girl.
Who isn't?
I don't think we've met. I'm Ross.
I know. You're the guy who
wouldn't chip in for the handyman.
Never mind.
No, I actually thought it was unfair
the way everyone reacted.
I mean, you had just moved in.
I had just moved in!
Thank you!
Listen, um...
- Jen.
I know this may sound a little:
But, uh, would you want to grab
a cup of coffee sometime?
Sure, that would be nice.
- Um...
- Oh.
My number's on there.
Give me a call.
I will give you a call. Heh.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
I forgot my paper.
- That was amazing.
- Ugh.
Phoebe and Gary are so gonna
hear about this at dinner.
That was amazing.
We are the hottest, huh?
No one is hotter than we are.
- We're the best.
- No, you're the best.
Aw.
I am the best.
Hey, guys.
What you been doing?
Hey, Joey, isn't that the girl
who waved at you the other day?
I don't know,
but I can see through your sheet.
Yeah. Yeah, that's her.
But you know what? It doesn't matter.
- I'm never gonna meet her anyways.
- Why?
Because it's impossible
to find her apartment!
She lives in some hot-girl
parallel universe or something.
What are you talking about?
She lives on the 2nd floor,
7th apartment from the left.
No, no, no, she lives on the 3rd floor,
8th apartment from the left.
No. Those first two windows,
that's the lobby.
That other window is the stairway.
You've been counting wrong.
I did not know that!
Thank you, Monica.
I almost lost another girl
because of counting!
So, uh, you ready?
- Yeah, I'll just get my coat.
- Okay.
- Could you get that?
- Sure.
- Joey...?
- Aah! No! No!
Uh, first, I would like to say thank you
for agreeing to see me again.
That's, uh, quite all right.
But I feel obligated to tell you
that this meeting is being videotaped.
Okay. Um.
Well, first, I would like to start
by apologizing for kissing you...
...and, uh, for yelling at you.
Fair enough.
Now, you're probably going to hire
one of the people who, uh...
Who did... Who did not, um, ahem...
...yell at you and storm out.
And I think that's a big mistake.
And here's why.
I made a huge fool of myself,
and I came back. That shows courage.
When I thought you wanted sex
in exchange for this job, I said no.
That shows integrity.
And I was not afraid
to stand up for myself...
...and that shows courage.
Okay, ahem.
Now, I know that I've
already said courage...
...but you've got to have courage.
And, um, finally...
...when I thought you were making
sexual advances in the workplace...
...I said no, and I was not litigious.
So there you go. You got courage...
...you got integrity,
you got courage again...
...and not litigious.
Look, Mr...
- Zelner.
- Zelner!
I knew that!
Oh, I knew that.
I really, really want this job.
And I think I would be really good at it.
You know what?
I may regret this, but, uh...
...I'm gonna give you a shot.
- Oh, you are?
- Mm-hm.
- Really?
Oh, thank you. Oh, God!
Would it be inappropriate
if I gave you a hug?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Well, how about a handshake? Ha-ha-ha.
Aah! Oh, God! I'm sorry!
Oh, God, I did not mean to touch that!
I mean, you!
There! Uh, there. Um...
Okay, so, thank you.
I'm gonna leave. Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Hey, I'll see you Monday.
- Are you tired?
- You better believe he's tired...
...after the day we had!
If you know what I mean.
Do you know what I mean?
Honey? The tortilla chips
know what you mean.
So, uh, Chandler,
do you like that badge I got you?
Oh, yeah, it's so cool.
Now, I gotta go.
Officer Bing's got a 10-100.
That's pee-pee.
Phoebe, you have a twig in your hair.
Oh, ha, ha. Um...
We kind of took a detour
on our way over here.
We were strolling through the park
and no one was around, so...
- You didn't.
- We did!
Ha, ha. We violated section 12,
paragraph 7 of the criminal code.
- The park, huh?
- Ha, ha.
- Public place.
Uh-huh.
I hear you.
Can you excuse me for a second?
Hi, Chandler.
Monica, this is the men's room.
Isn't it?
Yes, it is.
But see, I've always found
the men's bathroom very sexual.
- Haven't you?
- No.
And if I did, I don't think
we'd be going out.
This is getting ridiculous.
- Come on, we can't let them win!
- Uh...
We've proved that we are hot, okay?
So why are you obsessed about this?
Phoebe and Gary are in that "can't keep
their hands off each other" phase!
- So?
- So.
It makes me really sad that
we're not really there anymore.
Oh, is that what
this has all been about?
Wasn't it a lot more exciting
when we were, you know...
...all over each other all the time?
Yeah, that was great.
That was really great.
But to tell you the truth,
I'm more excited about where we are now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I've never been in a relationship
that's lasted this long before.
To get past the beginning and
still want to be around each other?
I think that's pretty incredible.
And the fact that
this is happening with you...
...I think that's pretty exciting.
That's so sweet.
I know that I was acting
a little crazy...
...but I feel the same way.
- Mm?
You know what I just realized?
You just freaked out
about our relationship.
- Pfft, I did not.
- Yes, you did!
Admit it. You freaked out!
I freaked out a little.
A little?
You freaked out bigtime, okay?
And I fixed it!
We have switched places.
I am the relationship king,
and you are the crazy, irrational screwup!
And now we're back.
I cannot believe Ross is buying this.
- Thank God. I can't watch him anymore.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- You guys ready for the movies?
- Yeah.
Oh, by the way, thank you for
loaning us Pamela and Yasmine.
Man, they cannot get enough!