Hey, hey, hey, hey.
None of that.
Not while you're living under my roof.
What?
Look, just because I know about you two
doesn't mean I like looking at it.
Aren't you supposed to be
at an audition for another hour?
Well, I'm sorry if I'm not
a middle-aged black woman.
And I'm also sorry if sometimes
I go to the wrong audition.
Okay, look, if I have to pretend
I don't know about you two...
...then you two are gonna have to pretend
there's nothing to know about.
Okay, sorry.
I can hear that.
Rachel's at work.
I can still hear you.
- Hey.
Hey. What's that?
Yeah, my mom sent me a family heirloom
that once belonged to my grandmother.
Can you believe it?
A year ago I didn't even have a family...
...and now I have heirlooms
for crying out loud.
- Oh, God!
- Aah!
Oh, soft.
- Is this mink?
- Yeah.
Why would my mother send me a fur?
Doesn't she know me but at all?
Plus, I have a perfectly fine coat that
no innocent animals suffered to make.
Yeah, just some 9-year-old Filipino kids
who worked their fingers bloody...
...for 12 cents an hour.
That didn't happen, I made that up.
- Hey.
- Ross?
Ross, you can't put up flyers in here.
How come? Everybody else does.
You can't.
What is that?
Oh, uh, I'm getting rid
of a couple of things.
This is all of your things.
Yes, yes, it is.
No, but it's good. Emily thinks
we should get all new stuff.
Stuff that's just ours.
Together, you know, brand new.
So basically this is a "getting rid
of anything Rachel ever touched" sale.
Touched, used, sat on, slept on...
I'll take it all.
Hey, Ross, you're okay with that?
Look, if I can just do what Emily wants...
...and get her to New York,
I'm sure everything will be fine.
Okay, but don't you think
that's a little extreme?
- After what I did, can you blame her?
- Oh, my God. You got off easy.
When my friend Sylvie's husband
said someone else's name in bed...
...she cursed him
and turned his thingy green.
What is he doing?
Emily thinks Ross' furniture
has got Rachel cooties?
- Calm down, Joey.
- No.
Everything's getting all messed up,
you know?
Emily won't let Ross see Rachel.
We're not gonna stop seeing Rachel,
hence, Ross stops seeing us.
Oh, I hate this. Everything's changing.
Yeah, I know.
We're losing Ross, Joey said "hence."
I'm not happy about this either, but,
you know, if Ross says he's happy...
...then we just have to keep our feelings
about Emily to ourselves.
Are you cool with that?
No.
But, you know, I'm an actor.
I'll act cool.
Ooh. Oh, God,
storage rooms give me the creeps.
Monica, please, hurry up, honey, please.
If you want the little round waffles...
...you've gotta wait till I find
the little round waffle iron.
- I want the little round waffles.
- All right.
Here it is.
Right underneath the can of bug bomb.
I wonder if the best place to put something
that cooks food is underneath the poison?
Okay, you know what? I'll have toast.
Fog him! Fog him!
I don't know what I'm gonna do
about this coat.
I'll take it.
- That might work.
- Oh, yeah, ha, ha.
Huh? All right, what do you think?
You're on in five, Ms. Minnelli.
No, no, no, it's just a bit sudden.
No, it's great, okay?
I am totally on board.
I love you too. All right, bye.
- What's the matter, Ross?
- Nothing. No. Oh, uh, actually...
...great news. Heh.
Um, just got off the phone with Emily...
...and looks like I'm moving
to a new apartment.
Whoo-hoo!
- Why?
- Well, her thought is... And I agree.
- Fresh new furniture,
why not a fresh new apartment?
Her cousin has this great place to sublet.
It's got a view of the river on one side
and Columbia on the other.
That's way uptown.
That's like three trains away...
...which is great.
I love to ride that rail.
So you're really okay with this?
Yes, yes. I mean,
it's kind of far from work...
...but, uh, you know,
I'll get so much done on the commute.
I've been given the gift of time.
That's so funny, because last Christmas
I got the gift of space.
We should get them together
and make a continuum.
Now he's moving?
Man, what is Emily doing to him? Ow!
He's not even here.
You guys. You guys.
We were just in the storage area
and we saw this really creepy man.
He was like this crazy-eyed,
hairy beast-man.
He was like a Bigfoot
or a yeti or something.
He came at us with an ax,
so Rachel had to use the bug bomb on him.
Yeah, I pulled the tab
and I just fogged his yeti ass.
Uh, like, dark hair, bushy beard?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you fogged Danny.
Ugh, please. We did not fog Danny.
Who's Danny?
Danny just moved in downstairs.
He just got back from this four-month trek
in the Andes. Nice fella.
Oh, he's nice. He's nice.
You know, you always...
...stick up for the people we fog.
- Yeah?
- Hi.
You might not remember us,
but we are the girls that fogged you.
- We're really sorry we fogged you.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Hi, uh, just so you know,
we didn't mean to fog you.
We actually thought you were
like a yeti or something.
Okay.
Yes?
Hi. Ahem, sorry to bother you...
...but I don't think that we can accept
your acceptance of our apology.
It just doesn't really seem
like you mean it.
Okay.
Wow. That guy is so rude.
Really. What is with that guy?
I mean, you'd forgive me
if I fogged you.
Well, you did, a little bit.
Oh, my God, honey. I'm so sorry.
- I totally forgive you.
- Really?
- Hey.
So listen, you know my friend Chris
who owns the crematorium?
Crematorium Chris? Sure.
Well, he said that he would cremate
my fur coat for free...
...if I, um, you know, bring in
the next person I know who dies.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Look at these pelts.
Don't get too attached.
She's having it cremated.
Wha...?
Phoebe? Ha. Honey?
Honey, I know you're quirky, and I get
a big kick out of it. We all do, actually.
But if you destroy a coat like this...
...I mean, that is like a crime
against nature.
Not nature. Fashion.
This is fashion?
Okay, so to you, death is fashion?
That's really funny.
Yeah, here's Phoebe, uh...
...sporting, you know,
cutting-edge hairy carcass...
...from, you know,
the steel traps of wintry Russia.
I mean, you really think this looks good?
Because I do.
I know, I miss you too.
I can't wait to see you.
I love you. Bye.
Okay, what is in here, rocks?
No, this is my collection
of, uh, fossil samples.
So rocks.
I'm really gonna miss this apartment.
Heh.
You know, Ben took his first steps
right over there.
Hey, remember when I ran into this thing
and it kind of knocked me out a little?
I love this place.
To tell you the truth,
I wish I didn't have to move.
Uh, are you saying that you're not
entirely happy about this?
Well, I mean, if, uh,
Emily gave me a choice...
You do have a choice.
Ross, why are you listening to her?
Are you crazy?
What?
It's not right what Emily wants you to do.
She is totally... Ow!
Stop pinching me.
You guys said I only had to keep my mouth
shut as long as Ross was happy, right?
Well, he just told me
that he's not entirely happy.
What's going on?
We all hate Emily.
- No.
- No, Ross, we do not hate Emily.
We just think that
you're having to sacrifice...
...a whole lot to make her happy.
Yeah.
We just think that maybe
she's being a little unreasonable.
Yes, yes, unreasonable.
Unreasonable?
How about we have this conversation
when one of you guys gets married?
You have no idea what it takes
to make a marriage work.
It's about compromise.
Do you always like it? No.
Do you do it? Yes.
Because it's not all laughing,
happy, candy in the sky...
...drinking coffee at Central Perk
all the time. It's real life, okay?
It's what grownups do.
I think he's right.
You guys hang out at the coffeehouse
way too much.
- God, I feel so guilty about Ross.
- Ugh, I know.
I kind of feel like it's my fault.
Kind of?
If you just kept this to yourself,
none of this would have happened.
Well, I'm keeping so many things
to myself these days...
...something was bound to slip out.
Well, I think it's very brave
what you said.
I can't sit here anymore.
I have to walk places.
Pheebs, what are you doing with the coat?
How about the whole animal rights thing?
Well, ahem, I've been reading up,
and for your information...
...minks are not very nice.
Okay, I admit it.
I love this coat, okay?
It's the best thing I've ever had wrapped
around me, including Phil Huntley.
Remember Phil Huntley? He was fine.
Hi.
- So you like the short hair better?
- What?
Yeti? Uh, Danny?
I had to cut my hair to get rid of the, uh...
...fogger smell.
- Oh.
Listen, I'm so sorry.
I would have never fogged you...
...you know, if you hadn't looked so...
You know, um...
Absolutely. Some people
are just into appearances.
- What?
- That's cool. That's cool.
What...? Hey, whoa, no, no, no,
that is not cool.
You don't even know me.
Come on. You got the shopping bags
and the Saks catalogue.
So from that, you think
you've got me all figured out?
Well, you don't.
You know, I could have toys
for underprivileged kids in here.
Do you?
Well, you know,
if kids like to play with capri pants.
Okay.
And stop saying that. I hate that.
Fine. I judged you.
I made a snap judgment.
But you did it too, and you're worse...
...because you are sticking
to your stupid snap judgment.
You can't even open up your mind for a
second to see that you might be wrong.
What does that say about you?
That pizza place
across the street any good?
- What?
- I'm hungry.
You wanna get some pizza?
You can keep yelling if there's more.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Stop saying that. I hate that.
Uh, Ross?
- Are you still mad at us?
- Yup.
Oh, good, because we have
an "I'm Sorry" song. Ha, ha.
You know what?
I'm really not in the mood.
Look, Ross.
I feel really bad. I mean,
you're going through all this stuff...
...and I just acted like a jerk.
- Yeah, we are so sorry.
- You're stepping on the song.
Look, we were way out of line, all right?
We totally support you.
Whatever you decide, whatever you do.
Okay, now you're just taking lines
right out of the song.
Look, this is hard enough, okay?
I really need you guys right now.
Yes, exactly. And that's why...
Why don't you come over tonight,
and I'll make you your favorite dinner?
Come on.
Okay.
Thanks, you guys.
Pheebs, are you wearing fur?
Okay, let's get some perspective, people.
It's not like I'm wearing
a seeing-eye dog coat.
You know, Ross, I, uh, think I kind of
understand why I lost it today.
- You do, huh?
- Yeah, you see, um...
...I'm an actor, right?
So I gotta keep my emotions
right at the surface, you know?
I got a lot of balls in the air,
you know what I mean?
It's tough. Guys like me, you know,
you wander around, you're alone.
What are you talking about?
I'm not sure.
- Hi.
- Hey, look at you. Where have you been?
Oh, I went to have pizza. With Danny.
- How did that happen?
- That yeti is one smooth talker.
I hope you're not too full,
because dinner's almost ready.
Yeah, you know, I think I'm probably
just gonna hang out in my room.
- Oh, no.
- Why?
Come on, you guys.
Listen, if Emily knew I was here having
dinner with you, she would flip out...
...and you know it.
It's okay. I really... I don't mind.
Wait, wait, wait. You know what?
Just stay.
Please.
It would really mean a lot for me
if you stay.
Ross, I just...
Rachel, please, just have dinner with us.
Okay, Joey, it's okay. Settle down.
All right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You see, Rach, I'm an actor.
Hey. Hey, look. Ugly naked guy's back.
We haven't seen him in so long.
Oh, God.
I really missed that fat bastard.
Wow. This is so weird.
I just realized this may be the last time
we're all hanging out together.
It's almost as if he knew.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Hi, Emily.
Yeah, uh, you tracked him down.
Hold on one second.
Hey.
Yeah, yeah, we're, uh, just having dinner.
Uh, yeah, sure, hold on.
She wants to say hi. Hold on.
Hi, Emily.
Hello, everyone.
So who am I saying hello to?
Well, uh, I don't know
about who's here...
...but I can tell you for damn sure
who's not here, and that's Rachel.
Well, I should hope not.
Ross knows better than that by now.
You know what? Uh, Rachel is here.
She's there?
Oh, yeah, there she is.
Yeah. Yeah, she's here.
Ross, take me off speakerphone.
- Hi.
- How could you do this to me?
I thought I'd made my feelings
about Rachel perfectly clear.
Look, Emily, I'm just having dinner
with my friends, okay?
- You obviously can't keep away from her.
- That's ridiculous.
Look, I'm moving for you.
I'm cutting friends out of my life for you.
Please, just get on the plane
and come to New York, okay?
You'll see you're the only person
I want to be with.
I'll feel better when I'm there
and I can know where you are all the time.
Well, you can't know where I am
all the time.
Look, this marriage is never gonna work
if you don't trust me.
You're right.
So... can you trust me?
No.
I think it's going okay.
Looks like he's smiling.
How can you tell?
You can only see the back of his head.
You can totally tell.
Here, look, watch me.
Smile. Frown. Smile. Frown. Smile.
Well, I guess that's it.
Why? What happened?
My marriage is over.
- What?
- Oh, sweetie.
Oh, look at you, you're shivering.
Here.
Ross, honey,
is there anything we can do?
Yeah.
You can help me
get my furniture back from Gunther.
Okay, stop tormenting me.
This is mink, okay?
They're mean, and they hate squirrels.
And, you know, most of these
probably wanted to be coats.
All right, fine. No, I get it. Here.
You take it.
Are you happy now? I'm cold.