Hello?
- Hey, Joey!
- Hey, Pheebs.
Can you do me a favor?
I forgot the PIN to my ATM card.
Can you get it for me?
Sure. Where is it?
Uh, I scratched it on the ATM machine
on the corner.
Oh, so you're 5-6-3-9?
That's it! Thanks.
- Wanna talk to Chandler?
- Let me talk to him.
He didn't believe in my movie...
...which is a big mistake,
because it is real. Real.
I've tried to apologize.
If I can't do it on the phone,
I'll go and do it in person.
I heard that. Uh, can you put him on?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Don't come out here.
I support you 100 percent
and I wanna prove that to you in person.
I got that. I forgive you.
Don't come out here.
You haven't taken
my calls for a week.
I'm totally over it. Friends forever.
Don't come out here.
Would you mind doing
a picture with us?
Uh, what was that?
Uh, Entertainment Tonight.
Good talking to you
and don't come out here.
Monica?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Phoebe?
I'm so sorry.
Have you been here long?
That's okay.
What the hell took you so long?
You can't tell Chandler.
I ran into Richard.
- Which Richard?
- The Richard.
Richard Simmons? Oh, my God!
No, my ex-boyfriend Richard.
You know, the tall guy, mustache.
Okay, that actually makes more sense.
How was it?
It was really nice. We talked
and I had lunch with him.
That's weird. I dreamed
you had lunch with Richard.
- Really?
- Again, Richard Simmons.
Go on.
The strange part was
he was really nice...
...and he looks great,
but I didn't feel anything.
So why can't we tell Chandler?
It'll freak him out and tomorrow's our
anniversary. I don't wanna spoil it.
I can't believe you guys
have lasted a whole year!
Wow, I owe Rachel 20 bucks.
What?
On a totally different bet.
Hey!
- It's almost our anniversary!
- I know.
One year ago today, I was just
your annoying friend Chandler.
Aw, now you're just
my annoying friend Chandler.
- Huh.
- I got you a gift.
- It's not till tomorrow.
- I know, but you have to open it today.
Okay! There you go!
- It's two tickets to Vegas!
- Wow.
Yeah! For this weekend!
It'll be perfect.
You'll see Joey, plus, we'll start
our celebration on the plane.
We can call it our "Plane-a-versary."
We have to?
This is great, but Joey didn't want
any of us there.
He doesn't want us to go to any trouble.
He'll be excited when we surprise him.
Plus, we get to have
our own "Anna-Vegas-ry"!
"Anna-vada-versary!"
I think we should see other people.
We can go, right?
Great idea.
I'm gonna go too!
Pheebs, it's kind of
our anniversary.
You won't ditch me
like you did with London.
Ditch you?
You were pregnant...
Uh-huh. Great story. I'm going.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Listen, this weekend we're all gonna go
to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
Including me!
Do you wanna go?
I can take a couple days off work.
Of course you can take a couple days
off, because this trip includes me!
I've got a presentation tomorrow.
I can't miss that.
I've got tickets to the Van Gogh
exhibit. I waited a year for this.
- Rach, maybe we can fly out Saturday?
- Sounds great.
I'll call the airlines.
That'll be nice to have
the apartment to myself.
To walk around naked.
No, so I can be by myself.
Have a little alone time.
Naked alone time.
Just because I'm alone doesn't mean
I wanna walk around naked.
You live alone,
you don't walk around naked.
Uh-huh. Why does it takes me so long
to answer the door?
So far, is this trip to Las Vegas
better or worse than the trip to London?
So far, it's pretty much
the same, Pheebs.
What about after I give you
these candies?
- I guess it's a little better now.
- Ha, ha.
Las Vegas, 1. London, 0.
I'll be back.
Happy Plane-a-versary.
Aw. I love you.
- Can I give you your present now?
- Okay!
Oh, don't tell me I did this.
I love "I forgot the present" fake-out!
How about "I did forget the present,
forgive me" not fake-out?
You can give it to me
when we get back.
This is the worst thing
that could happen.
You decided to tell him
about the Richard thing.
What "Richard thing"?
Oh, no.
Simmons. Go with Simmons.
I ran into Richard yesterday.
He asked me if I wanted to go
for a bite and I did.
I didn't tell you
because you'd get mad...
...and I didn't wanna spoil
our anniversary.
I'm not mad.
Really?
So you bumped into Richard.
You grabbed a "bite."
No big deal.
Great.
Okay, London, 1.
Ooh.
Hmm.
Oh, look what happened.
Huh, check me out.
I'm in my kitchen...
...naked.
I'm picking up an orange.
I'm naked.
I'm lighting the candles.
Naked. And carefully.
Oh, my God! That's Rachel, naked!
I can't look at that.
I am looking at this.
Okay, vivid colors,
expressive brush strokes.
Unless she wants me
to be looking at that.
She knows I'm home.
She knows I can see her.
What kind of game is she playing?
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
Oh, Dr. Geller.
Stop it. You're being silly. Ha, ha.
Or am I?
Love to love you baby
Ow
Darn it!
Hey.
May I come in?
Uh, yeah, if you want to.
Do you want me to?
Yeah, sure?
So do I.
Okay, Rach, before anything happens...
...I wanna lay down a couple
of ground rules.
This is just about tonight.
I won't go through with this
if it'll raise the question of "us."
I just want this to be...
...about what it is.
And, um...
...what is that, Ross?
The physical act of love.
What, are you crazy?
So you weren't trying to entice me
just now with your nakedness?
Oh, God. You saw me?
You weren't trying to entice me
with your nakedness?
No!
You actually thought
I wanted to have sex with you?
No!
No.
No, no, no, no.
Hey, you guys, wait! You guys.
This place is much better than London.
A lady dressed like Cleopatra
gave me this.
Ninety-nine cent
steak and lobster dinner. Huh.
You don't eat animals.
For ninety-nine cents I'd eat you.
I can totally settle down here.
It's got everything I could ever want.
Including Joey! Look!
Look! Hey!
Oh, my God.
Hey, Joey!
- Wow!
- Hi.
Love your condoms, my man.
Why are you here?
I told you not to come.
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
Uh, because I'm shooting a scene right now.
I play a gladiator.
Hold on a second. Can we cut?
My friends are here.
I'm gonna take a break.
Who are you talking to?
The director.
Uh, her.
All right, it's not a gladiator movie.
I work here.
Why? What happened?
The movie shut down.
Ran out of money.
I'm working here till it starts up,
if it ever does.
- I'm so sorry.
- Such a drag.
Sorry I didn't tell you. I'm sorry.
Apparently there's
a new policy of not sharing.
- I knew you weren't okay with that.
- So you're a gladiator!
What's going on?
- Monica had lunch with Richard.
- Dawson?
No...
But that would've been so cool!
Her boyfriend Richard.
It meant nothing. After all this time,
how can you not trust me?
When you go lunching with hunky men
and don't tell me!
You're right. I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
Thanks.
- Aw, there we go.
- Now I love Vegas.
I promise you next time
I absolutely will tell you.
"Next time"?
Ooh, so close.
There won't be a next time.
You cannot see him again.
I cannot see him?
You can't tell me what to do.
That's funny, I think I just did.
If you act like this,
I won't be around you.
- Fine.
- Happy anniversary!
Guys, please! Come on, come on.
This is obviously
a misunderstanding.
- No, it's not.
- What're you talking about?
Don't look at me. I just work here.
Okay, um, Ross? I'm a little warm,
so I'm gonna be taking off my sweater.
Now, I'm just letting you know...
...this is not an invitation
to the physical act of love.
Yep, that's hilarious.
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
You know, last night was
embarrassing for you too.
No, not really.
But you know,
I just don't embarrass that easily.
What? You totally get embarrassed.
No, I don't. Ross, I think I'm just
a more secure person than you are.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
Hey, lady!
I don't care how much
you want it, okay?
I am not gonna have sex
with you in the bathroom!
You know, in Roman times,
this was more than just a hat.
Really?
Yeah, sure, sure.
They would scrub the floors.
They'd use it to get the mud
off their shoe.
Sometimes underneath
the horse would get dirty.
So they would stick it right...
I can't believe this is how
I'm spending my anniversary.
I'll take you someplace nice.
A guy tipped me $100.
- Whoa!
- Yeah.
He was playing blackjack
for an hour and he won $5000.
Can you believe that?
If I won $5000, I'd join a gym.
Build up my upper body...
...and hit Richard from behind
with a stick.
Wait! Why don't I just
do what that guy did?
I'll take this $100,
turn it into $5000...
...and I'll turn that into enough
to get my movie going!
Good luck.
- I don't need luck. I've thought this through.
- I see.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I can't believe this.
This is like the worst night ever.
You had a minor setback
in your relationship.
Big deal. It's only Chandler.
I am so sorry.
This is crazy having
such a stupid argument.
I don't wanna see Richard.
So go fix it.
Find Chandler.
He's probably in your room.
Tell him sorry and you love him.
You're right, Phoebe.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Yeah! Las Vegas! Number one!
- Anybody lose this?
- Coming out.
Place your bet.
Dice her out.
Yellow 11. Pay the front line!
Hmm.
So, uh, I'm on my way
back to the bathroom.
All right, all right.
Just keep walking, all right?
What are you... I am sorry, sir.
I think he just really likes you.
Hey...
You know that teacher who had a baby
with her student?
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
Do you have any extra pants? Uh, my friend
seems to have had a little accident.
- Can I change 100?
- Changing 100.
- Good luck, sir.
- Thanks.
That's right.
- Thirteen.
- Hit me!
Oh, man!
Wait!
You are not gonna believe this!
I have found my identical hand twin.
What?
My identical hand twin!
What's an identical hand twin?
It was incredible. The dealer's hands
were exactly like mine.
It was like looking
at my hands in a mirror!
You sure you weren't
looking at your hands in a mirror?
Don't you see what this means?
I can forget about that stupid movie.
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
How?
I don't have it all worked out yet.
But it's gotta mean big money.
Come on, identical hands!
Again, I must go back to...
...how?
This is Vegas, man.
People will pay to see freaky stuff!
How much would you pay
to see this hand...
...twice? Huh?
I can't really put a price on that.
Are you un-supporting me again?
No. No.
I support you 100 percent.
I just didn't get it right away.
Now I'm caught up.
Identical hand twins.
It's a million-dollar idea!
- Hey!
- Pheebs!
I found my identical hand twin!
Oh, you're so lucky!
So where's Monica?
Did you guys make up?
- No.
- But she just came up here.
That was Joey.
I wonder where she is? It's so weird.
She's probably talking to Richard.
Would you stop that?
You know what she said
after her lunch with Richard?
She didn't feel anything for him.
She loves you.
- Really?
- Yes.
She feels terrible. She really wants
to make up. You've gotta find her.
Okay.
Good.
I should really start wearing hats.
Welcome to Las Vegas.
- Did you enjoy your flight?
- I did.
Thank you very much.
It was excellent.
- I hope you had a nice flight.
- Oh, it was the best.