I'm gonna get more coffee,
do you want anything, baby doll?
I'm fine. Thanks.
See, I can't pull off "baby doll," can I?
No, I think we learned that
from the "sugar lips" incident.
- I'm gonna get some tea.
- Okay.
How you doing, pumpkin?
Nope.
- So it looks like it's going well for you two.
- I know. Really well.
In fact, I'm gonna ask Phoebe
to move in with me.
- Oh, my God.
- What do you think?
I think that it's great.
When are you gonna ask her?
- Tonight. But don't say anything, okay?
- I swear. I promise. I promise.
My God, I'm so excited.
But listen, do not get her flowers, okay?
Because she cries when they die,
then there's the whole funeral.
- I'll see you after work, sweetie.
- Okay. Bye.
So, what movie should we see?
Gary's gonna ask you
to move in with him.
What? Really?
He told me at the counter.
He made me promise not to tell...
...but I couldn't hold it in any longer.
I can't believe this.
Right? Because it's fast.
Because it's so fast. It's fast.
- Relax. It's Phoebe, not you.
- Oh.
Good for you, Pheebs. Way to go.
- No, but it is fast, isn't it?
- No.
- I like him a lot but I don't think I'm ready.
- So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know. I'll just handle it.
I'll ask you to talk to him.
Me? Why me?
Because you are
so afraid of commitment.
You talk to him. Make him scared
like you, make him a man.
I'll try, but I'm not sure
what good it would do...
...because I'm less afraid of commitment
than I used to be.
That is so sweet.
Still terrified.
I'll take care of it no problem.
Hey, Ross, is, uh, Staten Island
really an island?
Uh-huh. That's why they call it
Staten "Island."
Oh, I thought it was like Long Island.
Also an island.
- Hey, what time is it?
- Two seventeen.
Wow, you realize we've been throwing
this ball without dropping it for an hour?
Are you serious?
Yeah, I realized it a half-hour ago,
but I didn't wanna say anything...
...because I didn't wanna jinx it.
Wow, we are pretty good at this.
Hey, we totally forgot about lunch.
I think that's the first time
I've ever missed a meal.
I think my pants are a little loose.
Hey, you guys. Uh, is Monica here?
- No.
Listen, um, I bought something.
I'm not sure she's gonna like it.
And it's gonna seem crazy...
...but this is something I've wanted
since I was a little girl.
You bought Shaun Cassidy.
No. I wish.
Okay, you ready?
Yeah.
Check it out.
- Oh, my God. What is it?
- What the hell is that?
- It's a cat.
- That is not a cat.
Yes, it is.
Why is it inside out?
Excuse me, but this is a purebred,
show-quality sphinx cat.
How much did you pay for that?
Well, it was a little extravagant,
but I got a good deal.
- Yeah, how much?
- Thousand bucks.
On a cat?
It's not a cat.
All right. Listen, ball boys.
My grandmother had one of these
when I was little...
...and it was the sweetest thing.
I mean, it was so cute, it would sit
in my lap and just purr all day long...
...and I would drag a shoe string
on the ground and it would chase it.
Free cats do that too, you know.
It's not a cat.
Look, guys,
I'm really excited about this, okay?
I don't care what you think.
I'm gonna go set up a little litter box
for Mrs. Whiskerson.
Well, what am I gonna call her? Fluffy?
Hey, do you wanna get something to eat
or, uh...
...see how long we can throw this ball
back and forth?
- Uh, the ball thing.
- Yeah?
Hey, Ross, wouldn't it be great
if we could go for like two straight hours...
...without dropping it?
Uh, yeah, it would.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
I have to pee.
And Rachel's in the bathroom.
Man, I didn't think we were gonna make it.
I know.
Don't switch hands, okay?
Hey, ladies.
What are you in here for?
Hey, Chandler, what are you doing here?
- Gary, I am here to report a crime.
- Yeah?
It is a crime that you and I
don't spend time together.
Ha, ha. What's up?
Uh, well, I heard that you were thinking
about asking Phoebe to move in with you...
...and I thought maybe we should have
a talk, you know, man to... well, me.
Sure, okay.
Um, are you crazy?
Are you insane?
If you live with Phoebe, you two
are gonna be, you know, living together.
Yeah, I considered that.
I just know it'd make me happy.
- Heh. You mean scared.
- No, I mean happy.
Scared happy.
- Chandler, what are you doing?
- I'm trying to open your eyes, my man.
Don't you see? If you live with Phoebe,
she is always gonna be there.
You're gonna get home, she's there.
You go to bed, she's there.
You wake up and oh, yes, she's there.
I know. I can't wait.
Were your parents happy or something?
Listen, Chandler, the way I see it...
...I was lucky enough to find someone
that I really love.
I just wanna be around her
as much as I can.
Wow, you know, when you say it,
it doesn't sound so scary.
- So you know what I'm talking about?
- Yeah, I think I do.
You know what?
You move in with her.
You move in right with her right now.
- Maybe I should move in with Monica.
- No, it's too soon for you guys.
You're right about that.
When they found the remains
of the Mesozoic mastodon...
...they discovered what appeared
to be the remains...
...of a Paleozoic amphibian in its jaws.
How did it get there?
Maybe this should be more
of a quiet game.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Joey, I left my watch
on the counter last night.
- It was here. Where is it?
- I don't know.
Well, come on, I'm late for work.
How do you know?
You don't have a watch.
Guys, could you stop throwing the ball
for one minute and just help me find it?
Oh, I don't know. Yeah, can't do it.
- What?
- Whatever you do, do not drop that ball.
- Yeah, we haven't dropped it in...
- Two hours, 27 minutes.
Really?
I'm not gonna be able
to make it in to work today.
Um, I don't feel very good.
Yes!
Wow, uh, for a second there,
I thought I was feeling better, but I'm not.
- Hey, Rach.
- Hey.
Check it out. Almost three hours
without dropping it.
Wow, congratulations.
That's quite a waste of time.
- Rach.
- Yeah.
You have scratches all over you.
What happened?
- Well, it's my cat.
- What?
- Oh, yeah, I got a cat.
- I don't want a cat.
- Oh, don't worry, it's not a cat.
- Yeah.
You guys, this cat is nothing like
my grandmother's cat.
It's not sweet. It's not cute.
I even dragged a string on the ground...
...and it just flipped out
and scratched the hell out of me.
And I swear... I know this sounds crazy,
but every time this cat hisses at me...
...I know it's saying, "Rachel."
Doesn't sound as crazy
as paying $1000 for a cat.
You paid $1000 for a cat
when you owe me 300?
Well, I was gonna let you play with it.
Hey.
Did you talk to Gary
about the moving in thing?
- Yes, I did, and I think you should do it.
- What?
He's a great guy and he loves you a lot.
You are a very lucky lady.
You are useless.
Freaking out about commitment
is the one thing you can do...
...and you can't even do that right. God.
Sorry. If he asked me,
I'd move in with him.
Oh!
Ooh, ooh, get out of here,
good-for-nothing.
- Hey, Chandler.
- Hey, Gar.
Hey, sweetie.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah. Okay.
- You look very pretty today.
- Thanks. Okay.
- Here's the thing.
- Yeah.
You know, I really want this relationship
to move forward.
Because if you're not moving forward,
you know, you're just moving backwards.
Now, that's not true. If you're not
moving forward, you're staying still.
And staying still is good. Watch this.
- Phoebe?
- Yeah?
I want you to move in with me.
That is so sweet.
But don't you think
that it's a little it's too soon?
I mean, there's so much
we don't know about each other.
Oh.
Oh, okay. I get it.
I don't want us to jump into something
that we're not ready for, you know.
Uh-huh.
I really don't want
to mess up what we have.
I'm just worried it's gonna
be a big mistake.
Yeah.
Which is why my answer is yes.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
You're so happy.
Monica, stop throwing it so hard.
We're on the same team.
Four hours? You guys have been
doing this for four hours?
That's right, baby.
- All right. Let me in.
- No, no. Don't do it.
What?
He's a dropper.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
I'm not a dropper.
It's really a three-person game,
you know?
It's throwing and catching.
All right.
Oh, oh, it's so hard.
Don't worry, guys.
It's not a cat.
Oh, my... Oh, good God.
I give up, you guys. I don't know
what I'm gonna do with this thing.
Baking it didn't help, huh?
Why don't you just take it back
to where you got it?
I tried. They won't take her back.
Maybe that's because
she's a minion of the Antichrist.
Rach, why won't they take it back?
Well, they said they would,
but would only give me store credit.
What am I gonna do,
get a thousand regular cats?
If you want, you can keep it
until you find out what to do with it.
No, Mon, that's not the point.
I'm out a thousand dollars...
...I'm all scratched up...
...and I'm stuck with this stupid cat
that looks like a hand.
Oh, my God.
The cat's made my eyes water.
Don't throw it to me.
My vision's been compromised.
Oh, God. Okay. Okay.
It's okay. Man, that was close.
Yeah, you almost overreacted
to something.
Hey.
- We have great news.
- We're moving in together. Isn't it great?
Yay!
- Congratulations.
- That's great.
- I know, I'm so excited.
- So am I.
Well, you're not more excited than I am.
No way. I'm the most excited. Ha.
Okay, I'll see you at the station later.
Okay, yeah, I'll see you later.
Don't forget about the moving-in.
So you're moving in with him?
What happened?
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad.
But maybe it'll be all right.
I do really like him a lot...
...and probably do it eventually anyway.
And plus, think of all the money
I'll save on stamps.
Why, do you write him a lot?
No, I just heard
when people live together...
...they split the cost
of stamps, don't they?
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's right.
Oh! Oh.
I'm sorry, the oven mitts
really freaked me out.
Hey, honey.
Did you find any apartments
in Brooklyn Heights?
No, nothing.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Nothing at all?
- No.
As soon as something opens up,
we'll move in.
Unless it doesn't have a pool.
I need a pool.
- Phoebe, can I talk to you for a second?
- Uh-huh.
Take a seat.
You okay? You feel all right?
Yeah, I feel great because
we're moving in together.
So you, uh...
You checked the paper for listings
in Brooklyn Heights, right?
You checked the Post?
Yeah, uh-huh, there was nothing.
- Can I get some water?
- In a minute.
- You checked today's Post?
- Um, yeah, today's.
Hmm. Because, uh, this is today's Post.
And, uh, these are the listings I found.
Brooklyn Heights, two bedrooms.
Brooklyn Heights, one bedroom.
Brooklyn Heights, Brooklyn Heights,
Brooklyn Heights.
Oh, are these for rent?
I thought people were just bragging.
Let me tell you what I think
might be going on here.
No, no, don't look at the table.
Look at me.
Okay, I think somebody asked someone
to move in with him.
And I think someone said yes,
but now she's having doubts...
...because things are moving too fast
for someone.
Does that sound at all possible to you?
Yes, yes. Yes, fine, I am someone.
You want me to say it? I have doubts.
I'm sorry.
- Phoebe.
- Yeah?
Phoebe, it's okay that you feel this way.
I mean, it is soon, and there's a lot of
things we don't know about each other.
I just figured everything I know about you,
I really like.
The things I don't know, I get to learn in a
place with both our names on the mailbox.
That's so sweet.
Sweetheart, but none of that matters
if it's too soon for you.
It's fine. We don't have to move in together.
I just want you to be happy.
- Living with you would make me happy.
- Phoebe, you don't have to say that.
No, I really wanna live with you.
I wanna move in with you.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Definitely, yes. Let's live in an apartment
that we both live in.
- Oh, that's great.
- Oh, wait, one sec. One sec.
Hey, you. Behind the glass.
Who are you looking at?
I've always wanted to say that every time
I was in one of these rooms...
...which was never.
Show cat. Quality show cat.
- Show cat.
- Oh, my God.
What's wrong with your baby?
That's not a baby. That's a cat.
- Ew, it's creepy looking.
- Oh, no.
No, it's actually very sweet.
It's very sweet. Look.
- Yeah. Do you want it?
- Ha, ha. No, I hate cats.
Well, so then what are you doing to me?
Okay?
Just get out of here, all right? Move on.
- Jeez.
- Wow, what an unusual cat.
Yes, thank you. Exactly. You want it?
Maybe.
I was thinking about getting a cat.
I was just gonna go to the shelter, but...
- Okay. Why not?
- Oh, terrific. That'll be $2,000.
- Ha. What?
- Okay, a thousand.
I thought you wanted me
to adopt your cat?
Well, I do, but you're gonna have to look
at this as more of an investment than a cat.
Okay, yeah. I just wanted a cat.
Okay, okay, okay.
Obviously, you know how to haggle...
...so I'm not gonna try and
take you on, okay?
So $800, and I don't call the cops...
...which I should
because you are robbing me blind.
Blind. Just take the cat,
leave the money and run away.
Just run away. Damn it. Ugh.
Can't you at least smile or something?
Okay, did anybody just hear that?
Anybody?
- I'm starving.
- Come on, guys. Suck it up.
We're closing in on 10 hours.
It's gut-check time.
I don't know who made you the boss.
We invented this game.
Please. I made this game what it is.
Not fun anymore?
I'm still hungry.
All right, there's some pizza at my place.
We can eat with one hand, right?
Are you with me?
- I am.
- All right, let's go. Come on.
Let's go, Team Monica.
All right, we can work out the name later.
Rachel, what is your cat doing
in one of my bowls?
It's not. I'm defrosting a chicken.
Oh, I sold, uh, Mrs. Whiskerson.
Oh, thank God.
- Did you get your money back?
- Yeah, $1500.
Wow, you made a profit?
- I just came for the red velvet pillow.
- Oh, yeah.
- There you go.
- Thanks, Rachel.
And, uh, don't forget,
you can come visit her any time you want.
Oh, good. Great. I'll keep that in mind.
Ahem, hey. So, what is this,
some kind of snake or something?
I really like waking up with you.
I like waking up with you too.
Oh, it's such a beautiful morning.
I could stay here all day.
That would be great.
- We could have breakfast in bed.
- Wait, just a second.
Oh!
Oh, no.
All right. Come on, Monica.
Look alive. Come on, look alive.
Oh, good. You're all up.
Phoebe, it's six o'clock in the morning.
Why aren't you at Gary's?
- Oh, yeah. That's over.
- What?
Come on, Gary's such a great guy.
Whatever the problem, you can work it out.
- He shot a bird.
- Oh, that is over.
- I'm sorry.
- That's terrible.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'll be all right.
- Oh, hey, here, Pheebs.
- Oh. Nah, I don't feel like playing.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just pretend that it didn't happen, okay?
No one needs to know.
Phoebe's not an official ball player.
I mean, only official ball players
can drop the ball.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Phoebe, honey,
you wanna get breakfast?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Okay, let's race.
First one there wins. Ha, ha.
- You guys wanna eat here?
- Yeah.
Oh, man, that was great, huh?
Can you believe how long
we threw that ball around?
It is amazing it lasted that long.
I know. My arm is killing me.
No, I meant with the dropper over here.
You know, how did I get
this reputation as a dropper?
I am anything but a dropper.
Ross.